[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This program pretends to be useful, while executing malicious code.", "correct_answer": "Trojan horse", "incorrect_answers": ["Logic bomb", "Worm", "Virus"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the following colors is  not used in the card game Magic: The Gathering?", "correct_answer": "Orange", "incorrect_answers": ["Blue", "Green", "Red"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The edible seaweed Irish moss contains this essential mineral used in the prevention and treatment of goiter.", "correct_answer": "Iodine", "incorrect_answers": ["Potassium", "Calcium", "Sulfur"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This 1998 tear jerker starring Julia Roberts and Susan Sarandon is about a terminally ill woman who has to come to terms with the new woman in her ex-husbands life.", "correct_answer": "Stepmom", "incorrect_answers": ["Pretty Woman", "Of Mice and Men", "Fried Green Tomatoes"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The number of weeks the Barenaked Ladies hit, One Week was #1 on the U.S. Billboard pop chart in 1998.", "correct_answer": "1", "incorrect_answers": ["10", "5", "3"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What kind of food is Amasi, a meal very popular in South Africa?", "correct_answer": "Fermented milk", "incorrect_answers": ["Fruit salad", "Cake", "Cheese omelet"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Johnny graduated from Hollywood High School in 1964.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In this movie Ayla, played by Daryl Hannah, teaches her new family to count all the way to ten.", "correct_answer": "The Clan of the Cave Bear", "incorrect_answers": ["Caveman and Cavewoman", "Way of the Caveman", "Land of the Tribe"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who directed the dramatic movie The Color Purple?", "correct_answer": "Steven Spielberg", "incorrect_answers": ["Spike Lee", "Ron Howard", "Robert Zemeckis"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "On what island does King Kong live?", "correct_answer": "Skull  Island", "incorrect_answers": ["The Island of no Return", "The Forbidden Island", "Crater Island"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In math and science a double tilda is often used as  a symbol. Which is symbolized by a double tilde?", "correct_answer": "Is approximately equal to", "incorrect_answers": ["Has the same atomic number as", "Has the same first derivative as", "Has the same atomic weight as"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Dogs sweat through their skin, like humans.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}]